Damn.
Adios.
We're going to need that Ark back now.
It's too late now, Mikhail.
Unfortunately for you,
the Ark is already a part of me!
Yuliy!
Shit!
Professor!
Hey, you okay?
I guess that was a bit of a rough landing.
What? That was a goddamn crash!
Yeah yeah, my bad.
I'm never letting you fly again!
Everyone!
Are you all okay?
Miss Ryouko?
And a tag-along.
Why are you all so reckless?
I'm pretty sure you don't have the right to talk.
It's love.
For Yuliy, specifically.
Enough of that, Dorothea!
Was my transmission helpful?
Oh yeah, that. The boss appreciated it.
That's good.
Right then.
All that's left is...
You absorbed the...
Precisely.
By making my body its vessel,
I've obtained its power.
My soul is now one with the Ark, and has become an existence that transcends mortal knowledge!
Amazing, Lord Yev!
Now you can cure everyone's disease!
A worthless endeavor.
With this power, eradicating the disease would be naught but a trifle.
However, that matter no longer concerns me.
I've been reborn!
I have been reborn as a stronger, more noble race!
Lord Yev?
Indeed,
I am no longer a mere vampire, but their new progenitor!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
You sure you haven't just gotten drunk on the Ark?
Oh? Can you really not sense the extent of my power?
What's wrong, Mikhail?
Does facing the first of the new vampires—
Lord Yev...
You're still Lord Yev, right?
Lord Yev would still be kind enough to cure us, wouldn't he?
Indeed.
There is no reason for you to fear the disease.
You need only forge a new pact with me now that I've become the progenitor.
Weakling!
Perhaps this means that only the noble are worthy of noble blood?
How will you fare, I wonder?
No.
No!
Stop!
Lord Yev!
What is there to be afraid of?
If my blood accepts you, you too will be reborn.
No!
Yevgraf!
Yuliy!
I already told you. We're staying together even if you try to fight me off.
Yuliy Jirov.
Why are you here?
Have you decided to become my pet after all?
The Ark can't be left in the hands of the likes of you!
Why, exactly?
Because it belongs to the Sirius?
Don't make me laugh.
After you didn't use this magnificent power for five thousand years?
And then in the end you even sealed it!
The being who gave you the Ark must have been filled with disappointment.
So I finally made use of it in your stead!
Shouldn't you be thanking me?
The old, weak race of vampires must first be destroyed.
Just as your race of Sirius was!
But there's no reason to despair.
Under me, a new race of vampires will be born
and rule over this world for all eternity!
What?
What? What is this?
Is this knowledge too?
No, that's wrong!
This essence...
It's flowing out of the Ark...
From my vessel...
What on earth...
He's been consumed.
Professor!
He's—
Don't talk.
He couldn't control the enormous power hidden in the Ark.
Why did you unseal the Ark, Yuliy?
Because I made a promise to Dad.
I promised that I would live with the Ark.
In order to prove that the new pride of the Sirius that Dad yearned for was right.
New pride?
Yes.
To coexist with all other races.
With humans,
and even with vampires.
Understood.
There's something I want to give you, Yuliy.
The Ark of Sirius?
Its counterpart.
We found it deep in Dogville's temple.
It isn't written of in the ancient text.
It was known only to the Sirius royal family, the owners of the Ark.
I believe it will allow one to control the enormous power of the Ark.
Yuliy.
Walk the path you believe in.
The Ark will surely respond to your feelings.
I know you can do it.
Brother!
Shit!
This isn't good.
We're losing altitude.
Why?
I've killed a bunch of people.
Lots of Sirius and lots of Jaegers.
So why did Yuliy say something like that?
He's come to realize something.
With the power of the Ark, something like that may become possible.
What's happening?
Is his body breaking down under the Ark's power?
You're not getting away!
Yuliy!
I finally found it.
The thing that I have to do.
My own path!
Brother!
You really like making trouble for your big brother, don't you?
Let's go!
I'm the one you need to worry about!
Brother!
You've held on to this for long enough, you bastard!
The Ark...
My power as the progenitor...
You blindly believed in the Ark.
That's why it consumed you.
Then what could you, the last surviving mutt of a dead race, possibly do alone?
I need the Ark because I can't do anything alone!
We're going to coexist with all other races.
If it's to further that goal,
I'll save even the vampires!
Don't be absurd!
If the alternative is accepting charity from a mangy Sirius,
I'd rather die a noble death!
As you wish.
How are your wounds?
So much for my dignity.
I said that I'd take care of revenge and everything else, but it looks like...
No!
Yuliy.
I'm happy now.
Finally...
I'll finally be freed from the power of the vampires that killed our mother.
Brother...
This is yours.
This is all I'll be able to do for you.
Yuliy.
Live.
Live with the Ark, and...
And...
I will.
I'll display it for all to see.
I'll show them the new pride of the Sirius.
You do that.
You really are... strong...
Brother?
Of course I am.
I'm...
I'm your...
Your little brother!
Brother!
Professor.
Professor Willard.
Yu... liy.
Is that...
The true form of the keeper of the Ark?
Yes.
I'm going to use this power for the sake of the world.
I believe that was the wish of the one who gave it to the Sirius.
Granting that wish will be my new way to live.
I see.
But, Professor...
Should I ever be consumed by the Ark like Yevgraf was...
If that time comes, please kill me.
As my second father.
Goodbye, Professor.
No,
Dad.
Yuliy...
Professor!
Thank god you're awake!
Where am I?
A hospital in Oodomari.
You were washed up on the coast and torn up pretty badly,
but the local fishermen found and saved you!
You've been asleep for four days!
I was—
Stop crying. You look pathetic.
They said that even when you were unconscious, you wouldn't let go of this.
Professor Willard,
what, uh...
What about Yuliy?
That's right, Professor!
What happened to Yuliy?
He's gone off.
Bearing the burden of a power that could make him a god or a devil all by himself.
Oh?
You're studying business?
Yes.
I go about two days a week to meet a college professor that my father introduced me to.
Father was quite surprised.
The moment his prodigal daughter comes back from Karafuto,
she's telling him to teach her business so she can inherit his company.
You sure have changed.
I've realized how childish and selfish my actions were.
But I don't believe my desire to help Yuliy was wrong.
It was nothing but trouble for me.
I'm sorry about that.
So in order to reach the outlook that Yuliy reached by a different path,
I've decided to go into the world and learn more about society.
I believe that's the shortest path from who I am now to a place where I can walk by Yuliy's side.
I've been told that she'll be under surveillance for the foreseeable future.
That's a waste of personnel. That girl doesn't know where the Ark is.
I guarantee it.
So Major, what is the Ark of Sirius anyway?
Mister Willard said the power of the Ark could make one a god or a devil.
Well, we humans are still letting our egos clash with each other and getting everyone hurt,
so maybe the Ark just isn't something we can be trusted with.
However, I've heard that Japan and the West will continue to pursue the Ark and Yuliy Jirov.
I don't think this world's going to change until something drastic teaches us all a lesson.
Compared to what drove that young man's decision,
our ways of thinking make us look like clowns.
So Major, what's your next assignment?
Not sure.
But whatever it is, I intend to do what only I can do.
I'll do all I can so that we can become a people that Yuliy will want to live alongside.
Yuliy,
you taught me that what I see is not everything,
and how one might examine a world alien to one's own.
So even if we go along different paths,
if we go down them following the same idea,
then surely,
surely,
they will one day overlap.
That is what I have faith in.
Among the mysteries of the Ark of Sirius
is the fact that there was no account of it being used during the last five thousand years.
Upon arriving in Dogville, I discovered the reason.
In its true state, no being of this earth can handle the Ark.
So to solve that, something was created as a counterpart to the Ark,
which gave the Sirius the ability to use its power.
But because of its unfathomable power, they decided that there was no need for them to use it yet.
Perhaps one of their descendants was to use it when the time was right.
And that descendant was Yuliy?
But thanks to that, the whole world's chasing him.
Including us.
Who would have thought that they'd prioritize the search for Yuliy over vampire-hunting.
Is that really the Jaegers' job?
Yuliy knew what he was in for when he unsealed and used the Ark.
Mister Willard.
All right.
It's from Headquarters.
A young girl thought to be a Royal
and a young man accompanying her were sighted in Khabarovsk.
Could that be...
Maybe.
But if he's with a Royal...
Could he have turned on us?
Of course he didn't!
Hurry up and get ready.
Headquarters wants us to capture him, right?
We're going to become Yuliy's enemies?
Are you okay with that, Professor?
Of course not.
That's why we're hurrying.
We'll find him faster than anyone else.
Don't you think that's something only we can do?
True.
What we do after that—
Let's think about that later!
I'll go check the ammo!
I'll bring the car out front!
Yuliy.
I want to see you.
I want to find you and watch you on your path.
You may not appreciate it, but your friends are coming to see you.
Hey, are you really going to come?
The elders have already given up.
But if you come and manage to get them all to listen,
they might decide to try to do something about that sickness.
I'll be waiting.
I'll keep waiting forever.
So please, Yuliy. Save us.
Here.
I wonder if they believe in me.
But if we don't all believe in each other, we won't be able to go a single step along this path.
Maybe everyone will call me a fool and get angry at me,
but I believe that's just part of the pride of the Sirius.
I'm going to end up seeing many worlds that refuse to exist alongside each other.
But...
So long as I don't give up on existing with them,
if I can show them what awaits them at the end of their path,
Then surely...
I'll believe in this power that's been granted to me.
Right, Brother?
I am the Sirius.
And I am
the one who protects and brings the world together.
If I'm to live by inertia
There's probably nothing wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night